Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Small Accessions, 1895-2006
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. Small Accessions 1895-2006
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company.
14.8 linear feet Extent: 10,000 Items
Established in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. Collection spans the years 1895-2006 and includes research reports, policy manuals, correspondence, writings and presentations and other materials documenting JWT's history and operations. It is an artificial collection that gathers a large number of small accessions and loose materials discovered during periodic cleanup and inventory of archival stacks and office spaces. Also included are some videocassettes and audio tapes. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing history.
RL.00748
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
In addition, original audiovisual materials are closed to patron use. Research Services staff need to produce use copies before contents can be accessed.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48-hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. Small Accessions were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 1987-2006.
Collection Overview
Collection spans the years 1895-2006 and includes research reports, policy manuals, correspondence, writings and presentations and other materials documenting JWT's history and operations. It is an artificial collection that gathers a large number of small accessions and loose materials discovered during periodic cleanup and inventory of archival stacks and office spaces.
Collection Arrangement
Collection has minimal arrangement that reflects an ongoing accumulation of materials.
Subject Headings
J. Walter Thompson Company; Advertising; Advertising -- United States; Advertising -- United States -- History; Advertising agencies; Advertising agencies -- United States; Advertising agencies -- United States -- History; Advertising -- Research; Videocassettes; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
Related Material
Related materials may be found in the following JWT collection held in the Hartman Center:
Account Files
Company Histories, Memoirs and Reminiscences
Corporate Documentation
Publications
Writings and Speeches
Description of Collection
- Inventory of Small Accessions, 1895-2006 and undated
  - Accession 790524A
    - The One Hour Lux Video Theatre, 1953 (Box 1)
  - Accession 790524E
    - Memos on JWT Advertising, 1955-1961 (Box 1)
  - Accession 790615
    - Creative Board Meeting Minutes, 1977-1979 (Box 1)
  - Accession 790626
    - The Creative Library (Records documenting development), 1978 and undated (Box 1)
  - Accession 790717B
    - Norman H. Strouse (Book written upon his retirement), 1969 (Box 1)
  - Accession 790808
    - John B. Watson correspondence, 1920-1960 (Box 1)
  - Accession 790814A
    - New Business Presentations, 1980s (Box 1)
  - Accession 790828B
    - Lux Radio Theatre as Broadcast Scripts, 1934-1955 (Box 1)
  - Accession 791004A
    - A Report on the JWT Training Program (Tom DeMint), 1979 (Box 1)
  - Accession 791004B
    - Policy (Paul A. Albright), 1956 (Box 1)
    - Various JWT documents, speeches, misc., etc., 1947-1961 (Box 2)
  - Accession 791022
    - JWT Artists--Samuel Yellin, James G. Tyler, Glen Michaels, Bruno Lucchesi, 1970s (Box 2)
  - Accession 791023
    - James W. Young Correspondence with Carl Byoir, 1918-1921 (Box 2)
  - Accession 791218A
    - Sam Meek, 1944-1946 (Box 2)
  - Accession 800411
    - Richard Lippold Sculpture Construction, 1958-1963 (Box 2)
  - Accession 800519
    - Communispond, 1971-1972 (Box 2)
  - Accession 810107A
    - Communications, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
    - Economic Report (Al Stridsberg), 1974 (Box 2)
    - Lord, Geller, Federico, undated (Box 2)
  - Accession 810422
    - Going Public Data, 1969 (Box 3)
  - Accession 810430
    - DeWitt Wallace Correspondence, 1975 Oct. (Box 3)
  - Accession 810706A
    - Financial Report: JWT Affiliated Companies, 1973 Nov. (Box 3)
  - Accession 810714
    - Milan Manager's Meeting, 1965 (Box 3)
  - Accession 810723A
    - Christmas Bonus Book, 1938-1969 (Box 3)
  - Accession 810807B
    - Directors, JWT Co., 1962-1968 (Box 3)
  - Accession 810807C
    - Pan Am Brochure, 1956 (Box 3)
  - Accession 810812
    - Billings, 1918-1963 (Box 3)
  - Accession 810813B
    - Colin Dawkins File, 1968 (Box 3)
    - International Facts Book, 1970 (Box 3)
    - Master Advertising Plan for JWT in South Africa in 1974, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Norman Strouse File--Talk to students at McKinley Jr. High School (December 5, 1968); their thank-you letters; Fragments about Mr. Resor, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Accession 811221
    - Fact Book: New York Office, circa 1980 (Box 4)
  - Accession 820107D
    - Chicago Office Plan and North America Assessment, 1979-1980 (Box 4)
    - Detroit Division: Operation Planning Review, 1979 Oct. (Box 4)
    - 1981 Operation Planning Review, 1981 (Box 4)
  - Accession 820111
    - The Corporate Goal: 1980 Corporate Priorities and Objectives, 1980 (Box 4)
    - Corporate Objectives, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Management Development Presentation, 1979 June (Box 4)
    - Shamplete (T-plan) Workshop Presentation, 1979 (Box 4)
    - T-Plan London, 1974 (Box 4)
  - Accession 820202
    - JWT Fellowship for School of Advanced International Studies, 1976 (Box 4)
  - Accession 820706
    - Operating Policies, 1981 Jan. (Box 4)
  - Accession 820720
    - Batch Walsh Treasurer's Office-- Includes balance sheets, exec committee agenda and resolutions, 1961-1965 and undated, (2 folders) (Box 5)
    - Memos to Stockholders, 1966-1967 (Box 5)
  - Accession 820723
    - International T-Plan Data (Roy Glah), 1970, (2 folders) (Box 5)
  - Accession 821118
    - Christmas Party, 1978 (Box 5)
    - Lord, Geller, Federico, Inc. (Includes Lansdowne), circa 1981 (Box 5)
    - Teledyne Water Pik and The Target Plan, circa 1980 (Box 5)
  - Accession 830516
    - Report on Organization Charting Project as a Prelude to Organization Structure Analysis, 1975 (Box 5)
  - Accession 830523
    - Appendices - Mr. Fickinger, 1977 (Box 5)
    - Wayne Fickinger: Chronological Files, 1980 Sept.-Dec. (Box 5)
    - Wayne Fickinger Correspondence, circa 1980-1981 (Box 5)
  - Accession 830524
    - Case Histories (Roy Glah), 1977 and undated, (6 folders) (Box 6)
    - JWT Profit Planning Guide, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Accession 830817
    - Affirmative Action Plans, various offices, 1977-1979, (5 folders) (Box 7)
  - Accession 830923
    - Your Show of Shows, 1976 (Box 7)
  - Accession 831010
    - Succession History, 1977-1983 (Box 7)
  - Accession 840106A
    - Manager's Meeting III: People Management, 1970 (Box 7)
    - New Business Seminar, 1975, (3 folders) (Box 8)
    - Summary of 1976 Research and Development Activities, 1976, (4 folders) (Box 8)
  - Accession 840106B
    - Wayne Fickinger Speeches (collected by Roy Glah), 1980-1981 (Box 9)
  - Accession 840125
    - Multinational New Business Targets; What is the proper philosophy for the use of Research and the Agency's role in providing it?, 1981 (Box 9)
  - Accession 840611A
    - "A Bit of Old New England in a New York Office Building", 1923 (Box 9)
  - Accession 840822B
    - Shirley Woodell Correspondence, 1984 (Box 9)
  - Accession 840920
    - Data Record, circa 1960 (Box 9)
  - Accession 841116
    - Office Christmas Cards, undated (Box 9)
  - Accession 841119A
    - Press Releases/Fact Sheets: JWT Central America and South America, 1969-1975 (Box 9)
  - Accession 841213
    - Advertisement Picture Negatives, undated (Box 9)
  - Accession 850307
    - Corporate Goals, Priorities, and Objectives, 1983 (Box 9)
    - Corporate Goals, Priorities, and Objectives, 1985 (Box 9)
    - LGFE Highlights, 1983 (Box 9)
    - JWT Mission Statement, 1984? (Box 9)
    - JWT Revenue and Growth Objectives, 1984 (Box 9)
  - Accession 850521
    - Inside JWT at the John Hancock Center, 1969 (Box 9)
  - Accession 850611
    - Advertising and Marketing Intelligence, 1979-1980 (Box 9)
  - Accession 850612
    - Tom Sutton 30th Anniversary; Board Meeting Brazil; Letter to Don Johnson from John Sharman, 1979 and 1983 (Box 9)
  - Accession 850619
    - Multinational Target Accounts: Board of Director's Meeting, 1980 (Box 9)
    - Operating Reviews: Asia Pacific, 1981 (Box 9)
  - Accession 850916
    - Account Management; T-Plan, 1982 and undated (Box 10)
    - "Marketing Plan" for Recruitment, 1979 (Box 10)
  - Accession 851218
    - Program of Activities - Latin American Managers Meeting, 1981 Sept. (Box 10)
  - Accession 860311
    - Corporate Objectives, 1976-1980 (Box 10)
  - Accession 860410
    - Counihan Memo re: Acquisition Plans for JWT, 1981 (Box 10)
    - JWT Formal Reporting Requirements, 1982 (Box 10)
    - Memos and lists re: election of officers, 1951-1978 (Box 10)
  - Accession 860416
    - T-plans (London, Chicago), 1974, 1976 (Box 10)
    - T-plan History (New York, Latin America, London), 1972-1973 (Box 10)
    - T-plan Chicago, 1977 (Box 10)
    - T-plan Documents (London, New York, Chicago, Canada), circa 1976 (Box 11)
  - Accession 860422
    - The Plan, 1985-1986 (Box 11)
  - Accession 860501
    - Manual, circa 1985 (Box 11)
  - Accession 860502B
    - Client Retention and Conflict, 1985-1986 (Box 11)
  - Accession 860825
    - JWT Competitive Framework: Where are we now? Situation Analysis, 1980 (Box 11)
    - JWT Domestic Communications Guidelines, 1979 (Box 11)
    - Market Force Proposal Volume I and II, circa 1980, (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - Review of Compensation and Benefits for Executives and other Exempt Employees, 1979 Nov., (2 folders) (Box 12)
  - Accession 870205
    - Art Project, 1970-1986, (2 folders) (Box 12)
  - Accession 870210
    - Detroit: Employee Anniversary Recognition, 1987 (Box 12)
  - Accession Unidentified Accessions
    - Accounts and Client Lists, 1983-1988 (Box 13)
    - Added Value Tax, 1971 (Box 13)
    - JWT Advertisement Booklet, undated (Box 13)
    - JWT Advertising Collection - Autos - Booklet, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 13)
    - Anniversary Program for JWT Chicago, undated (Box 13)
    - 1978 Annual Meeting, 1979 (Box 13)
    - Canter, Achenbaum, Heekin Inc. compensation study, undated (Box 13)
    - JWT Chicago and Direct Response Advertising, 1981 (Box 13)
    - Christmas, 1956-1993 (Box 13)
    - Christmas cards, undated (Box 13)
    - JWT Company Fund Incorporated: Minute Book, 1953-1962 (Box 13)
    - JWT Corporate Art Program Analysis, 1971 (Box 13)
    - JWT Corporate Policy, circa 1995-2001 (Box 13)
    - John Devine Interfiles, 1954 (Box 14)
    - JWT Directors Handbook, 1979 (Box 14)
    - Directors, Officers, and Partners, 1969-1995 (Box 14)
    - Display Write 3: Volume 1 and 2, undated (Box 14)
    - Eine neue Methode zur Sterilisierung von Säuglingsflaschen (JWT Frankfurt)--Milton antiseptic, by Christina M. Cousins, undated (Box 14)
    - Ford Advertisements, 1979, 1985-1986 (Box 15)
    - Former Directors, 1996 (Box 15)
    - JWT Frankfurt Office Accounts, 1964, 1970, 1990 (Box 15)
    - Press releases and clippings, 1985-2001 (Box 15)
    - JWT Group Mission Statement, 1983-1984 (Box 15)
    - JWT History, 1916-1966 and undated (Box 15)
    - House Ads, 1980s (Box 15)
    - JWT Information for Ellen Gartrell, 1994-1996 (Box 15)
    - JWT International Documents, 1973-1975, 1979 (Box 15)
    - JWT Internationals--Europe/Africa/Mideast and Latin America Briefing, 1976 (Box 15)
    - Interview with Ralph Rydholm, 1997 (Box 15)
    - Don Johnson files, Operations Committee meeting, 1985 (Box 15)
    - JWT Management Development Center - JWT Instructor Guide Year III, undated, (3 folders) (Box 15)
    - JWT Management Effectiveness Series III Participant, 1986, (2 folders) (Box 16)
    - JWT Management Effectiveness Series III Year 1, 1986, (3 folders) (Box 16)
    - Binder: JWT III Management Effectiveness Series Year 2, 1986, (3 folders) (Box 16)
    - JWT - Memoranda to Interfile, 1959-1983 (Box 16)
    - Microfilm JWT Advertisements (printouts), 1900s-1950s (Box 17)
    - Multinational Client Status Report, 1997 Mar. (Box 17)
    - Binder: Phil Mygatt, Creative Department, 1964-1971, (2 folders) (Box 17)
    - New Business Memos and Press Releases, 1994-1999 (Box 17)
    - JWT New Product Development Capabilities, 1974 Jan. (Box 17)
    - JWT Nonpublished Material - 1994 - Memo from Nancy Fitzpatrick, 1994 (Box 17)
    - JWT Office Anniversaries--New York and Chicago Offices, 1941-1989 (Box 17)
    - Office Reconstruction Organisation Committee Report, 1962 May (Box 17)
    - PC-File III: Database Program (Jim Button), 1985 (Box 17)
    - JWT Press Releases, etc., Spring 2000 (Box 17)
    - 1986 Purchase Influence Study, 1986 (Box 17)
    - JWT Records, 1960 (Box 17)
    - JWT Records - Chicago Library, 1963 (Box 17)
    - JWT Records - Misc., 1983-2001 (Box 17)
    - A Report to JWT Management: An Evaluation and Recommendations on the Future Role of the Office Services Function, 1972 Apr. (Box 17)
    - JWT: Reputation and Reality, 1978 Apr. (Box 17)
    - Second Quarter Communications Review, 1982 (Box 18)
    - Selection of JWT Line Officers in the U.S., circa 1978-1979 (Box 18)
    - Service Anniversary Recognition Reception, 2000 Mar. 6 (Box 18)
    - Service Completion and Birthday Lists, 1979 (Box 18)
    - Staff Meeting Minutes, undated (Box 18)
    - JWT Stockholder's Meeting, 1973 (Box 18)
    - Albert Stridsberg, 1969, (2 folders) (Box 18)
    - TGI and Simmons, 1974 (Box 18)
    - TV Violence, 1977 (Box 18)
    - Various JWT Documents, 1928-1999 (Box 18)
    - World Partners Council Proceedings: Fiuggi, Italy, 1995 Mar. (Box 18)
  - Accession 830217
    - Ethikos - JWT New York Office, 1968 (Box 19)
    - New York Office Annual Report By Department, 1966 (Box 19)
    - New York Advertising: A Framework for Future Operations, Five Years: 1975-1979; Memo from Chester A. Hopkins, 1975 May (Box 19)
    - Communications Planning and Review, 1975 Jan. (Box 19)
    - JWT: Technical Proposal: Agency Questionnaire, 1977 Mar. (Box 19)
    - JWT Company Domestic Communications Guidelines, 1979 (Box 19)
    - JWT Financial Relations Program, 1978 (Box 19)
    - Ford Star Jubilee Presents: "The Day Lincoln Was Shot", 1934 Mar. (Box 19)
  - Accession 99-385
    - Construction Plan for "New England Room", 1980 (Box 19)
    - Records Re: The New England Room, 1980 (Box 19)
  - Accession 99-386
    - Presentation and Analysis of Y&R, 1987 (Box 19)
  - Accession 93-217 or 93-218
    - EPCOT Conference Information, 1984, (2 folders) (Box 20)
    - Financial Operating Planning Reviews and Misc., 1984 (Box 20)
    - JWT Human Resources Organization Memo and Statement of Policy, 1992 (Box 20)
    - JWT International Memos and Documents, 1985 (Box 20)
    - Lifestages: A Study of Dramatic Changes in the American Consumer Market, undated (Box 20)
    - Misc. including Matched Giving Plan, undated (Box 20)
    - JWT Officers and Directors, circa 1980 (Box 20)
    - JWT Presentation beginning with "Post War Years" Video, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Accession 96-021
    - JWT/Interactive, 1996 (Box 21)
  - Accession 96-039
    - The Commodore and the Multinationals, undated (Box 21)
    - Eastman Kodak, undated (Box 21)
    - Group Photos (of staff members at Duke retreat/meeting), circa 1996 (Box 21)
    - James Webb Young (talk by E. Emmerling), undated (Box 21)
    - Leadership Through Innovation, storyboards--Three different storyboards rolled up separately, undated (Box 21)
    - Leadership Through Innovation, traveling exhibit--Includes Zubigraphics proposal and scripts, 1993 (Box 21)
    - Leadership Through Innovation, traveling exhibit photos, 1993 (Box 21)
    - Various photos of J. Walter Thompson, undated (Box 21)
    - What is a Brand?, 1980 (Box 21)
  - Accession 96-086
    - Management Leadership Program, 1983 (Box 22)
    - Microfiche index, undated (Box 22)
    - PPGH/JWT (Amsterdam) commercials (John Cleese; Milk, White Motor; Telecom audition; Bank--3; Dear Home; Do It Yourself). Umatic. NTSC, TRT: 10:00, undated (Box 22)
    - PPGH Story, slides, undated (Box 22)
    - JWT Chicago retrospective. VHS. TRT: 30:00., 1993 (Box 22)
    - Best Thompson Yet. Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00., 1984 (Box 22)
    - JWT Singapore radio commercials. Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00, 1990s (Box 22)
    - WPP Interim report, 1993 June (Box 22)
    - How Does PPGH Work? William Eccleshare, circa 1993 (Box 22)
    - Billings to clients, 1950-1964 (Box 22)
  - Accession 99-116
    - Society of Illustrators, report on JWT permanent art collection, 1986, (2 folders) (Box 23)
  - Accession 96-002
    - James Webb Young self-published books
      - A Footnote to History (Box 23)
      - Compleat Angler (Box 23)
      - Pills for the Angels (Box 23)
      - Full Corn in the Ear (Box 23)
      - Mirror for a Lady (Box 23)
      - His Girl and His Dinner (Box 23)
      - The Itch for Orders (Box 23)
      - Hometown Boy Makes Good (Box 23)
      - A Story Still Untold (Box 23)
    - Office party invitations, 1937-1969 (Box 23)
    - The Commodore N.Y.--brass door knob, undated (Box 23)
    - JWT News reprints, 1929-1969 (Box 23)
    - Script: Jack Benny Farewell Special, 1973 (Box 23)
    - Service Completion and Birthday Lists, 1979 (Box 23)
    - Media Leadership Workshop, 1985 (Box 24)
    - Flowchart, 1954 (Box 24)
    - Leadership in Total Brand Communications, undated (Box 24)
    - Section 13: JWT Training Policy (London Office), 1992 (Box 24)
    - Directors and Officers lists, 1988-1992 (Box 24)
    - Clippings and news releases, 1972-1994 (Box 24)
    - Human Resources Committee meeting, signed napkin, 1994 (Box 24)
    - Gender and ethnic studies, 1970-1980 (Box 24)
    - Media, 1970-1980 (Box 24)
    - Consumer Attitudes (Ehrenberg and Goodhardt), 1980 (Box 24)
  - Accession 810604
    - Letter from Stanley Resor to Mr. Johnson regarding speculative work, undated (Box 24)
    - Developing the Big Match Temperament (Human Resources workshop), 1994 (Box 24)
  - Accession 821118
    - 4-H Club Congress, 1961 (Box 24)
    - International service completion, 1984 (Box 24)
    - Miscellaneous commercials lists, undated (Box 24)
    - Kodak advertisements (old), undated (Box 24)
    - ALCOA corporate identity standards, 1988 (Box 24)
    - AT&T corporate identity standards, 1989 (Box 24)
  - Accession 23739
    - Production Billing Department, Standard Practices manual, 1967 (Box 25)
    - Cream of Wheat advertisement, undated (Box 25)
    - Account Coordinators Responsibilities, 1983 (Box 25)
    - Letter to Stanley Resor from F.A. Countway (President of Lever Brothers), 1925 (Box 25)
    - Communications Review, 1982 (Box 25)
    - Fascimile copies of People Magazine, 1974 (Box 25)
    - Management Committee Meeting, 1970 (Box 25)
  - Accession 850320
    - Accounts Obtained, 1960-1963 (Box 25)
    - Client Acquisitions and Resignations, 1957-1964 (Box 25)
    - Survival Guide to JWT Research and Planning Department, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Accession 841214
    - Rodolfo Otero Award, 1985 (Box 25)
  - Accession 860109
    - Latin American Objectives, 1980 (Box 26)
    - Latin American Management Meeting, 1981 (Box 26)
  - Accession 860113
    - Marketing Plan, 1982 (Box 26)
    - Standard Operating Procedure: Formal Reporting Requirements, 1980 (Box 26)
    - Evaluation Program, 1980 (Box 26)
  - Accession 860129B
    - Top 20 clients, 1981 (Box 26)
  - Accession 831024
    - Employee Attitude Study, 1972 (Box 26)
    - Future Role of Office Services Function, 1972 (Box 26)
    - People Philosophies, Practices and Styles, 1971 (Box 26)
  - Accession 830718
    - Legal Department: Corporate art purchases, etc., 1950-1957 (Box 26)
  - Accession 850412A
    - Memos on reorganization, 1973 (Box 26)
  - Accession 850401A
    - JWT Directors Handbook, 1974 (Box 26)
    - Company Objectives, 1982 (Box 27)
    - 1982-1983 Marketing Plan, 1982 (Box 27)
    - Dividend Program, 1972-1974 (Box 27)
    - Dividend Representatives Manual, 1972 (Box 27)
    - New Opportunity for JWT Dividends, 1972 (Box 27)
    - Lever Brothers and Dividend Opportunity, undated (Box 27)
    - Dividend recommendations, 1973 (Box 27)
  - Accession 860227
    - J. Walter Media, circa 1985 (Box 27)
  - Accession 830718
    - Corporate Art Program Analysis, 1971 (Box 27)
    - Media Department evaluation, 1978 (Box 27)
    - New York Office Fact Book, 1957-1979, (3 folders) (Box 28)
  - Accession 870415
    - The Meeting Club, 1968-1972, (5 folders) (Box 28)
    - JWT T-Plan, undated (Box 28)
  - Accession 821027
    - International Facts Book, 1971, (3 folders) (Box 28)
  - Accession 830718
    - New York Management Committee, minutes, correspondence, etc., 1969-1971 (Box 28)
  - Accession 850502B
    - Graybar Building descriptions, 1964 and undated (Box 29)
  - Accession 850419
    - Hill & Knowlton Beijing Office, undated (Box 29)
  - Accession 830718
    - New York Office Affirmative Action Plan, 1971-1978 (Box 29)
    - EA International, 1984-1985 (Box 29)
    - Soskin/Thompson Associates, 1979-1984, (15 folders) (Box 29)
  - Accession 810730D
    - Correspondence between J. Walter Thompson (person) and Merritt and Ella Oxenham, 1909-1927 (Box 29)
    - Howard Henderson files, miscellaneous, 1950s (Box 29)
    - Colin Dawkins files, 1940s and undated (Box 29)
    - Latin American Managers Meeting, 1981, (5 folders) (Box 30)
  - Accession 810205A
    - Mailers from Clark and Frere, undated (Box 30)
  - Accession 790808
    - Copies of Stanley Resor correspondence, 1923, 1951 (Box 30)
  - Accession 850225
    - New York Office orientation materials, 1969-1979 (Box 30)
  - Accession 870707
    - Balance sheets, 1968-1970 (Box 30)
  - Accession 851210
    - Tom Sutton: International Exchange Program, 1985 (Box 30)
  - Accession 851212B
    - Directors lists, 1969 (Box 30)
    - Word Processing manual, 1983 (Box 30)
  - Accession Unidentified Accessions
    - Cableshop, miscellaneous, 1980s (Box 31)
    - Roy Glah 35th Anniversary Certificate, 1992 (Box 32)
    - Photographs of JWT, Resor, Strouse, and Seymour, undated (Box 32)
    - Advertising Axioms, 1895 (Box 32)
    - Print advertisement, La Soie Naturelle, 1931 (Box 32)
    - Scrapbook: Some Notable People and Events in Your History, by Philip Ewald, 1961 (Box 32)
    - Advertiser, article on JWT Italy, 1996 (Box 32)
    - Advertising Age, Ford at 100, 2004 (Box 32)
    - JWT Backstage Spotlight, 1989 (Box 32)
    - Media Buying (Box 33)
    - Letter to Ron Kos, Hasbro, 1993 (Box 33)
    - Testimonial campaign (Lipton, California State Lottery, Mott, Orkin). VHS. TRT: 5:00, undated (Box 33)
    - Local Media Broadcast Department, staff profiles, undated (Box 33)
    - Slice of Life media pitch storyboards, undated (Box 33)
    - Adweek Agency of the Year, 1984 (Box 34)
    - Billion Dollar Startup launch press release, 2005 (Box 34)
    - CEO Messages, 1997 (Box 34)
    - Chrissie Barker obituary, 2006 (Box 34)
    - Ford advertisements (John devine), 1950s (Box 34)
    - Fortune Magazine article on Don Johnston, 1979 (Box 34)
    - Gallup reports, youth and baby boom markets, 1988-1991 (Box 34)
    - Getting on in Advertising, Charles, Raymond, undated (Box 34)
    - Index to News Bulletins, 1916 (Box 34)